{
    "id": "73917428558a4bdcbd583125111f6efa",
    "title": "Verbs And Their Complements",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He appears to be very ……………………… today.",
            "description": "Appear is a copular verb. We use adjectives, not adverbs, to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "angry",
                "angrily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ad360124e96421f8216c9e46f0966f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t want to continue her studies. It ……………………. a pity.",
            "description": "Seem can be used to talk about subjective impressions and feelings. Appear is mainly used to talk about objective facts.",
            "answers": [
                "seems",
                "appears",
                "looks"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6c5e65edf59429580f6604a41efe19f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She seems ………………………… an attitude problem.",
            "description": "We use a to-infinitive after seem.",
            "answers": [
                "to have",
                "having",
                "that has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "94c7dafa75cc4d98b7369446efbbc57f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hope …………………………. a good job soon.",
            "description": "We use a to-infinitive after hope.",
            "answers": [
                "getting",
                "to get",
                "that I get"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "de485a79d56f437fa3ee7ec2116ef7f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is not easy ………………………… smoking.",
            "description": "We use a to-infinitive after easy.",
            "answers": [
                "stopping",
                "to stop",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7355102ca9184f99b2a636a4abe9050c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I suggest ……………………………. a lawyer.",
            "description": "Suggest can be followed by an ing form or a that-clause. It cannot be followed by a to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "seeing",
                "to see",
                "that you see"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "913fb3a8fb4547d7bef6b6dedd47d6ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor recommended …………………………… down on my sugar intake.",
            "description": "After recommend you can write an ing form or a that-clause. You cannot write a to-infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "me to cut",
                "that I cut",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "99a24f06e75d4fa5a4422598f1f1fc39"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor recommended …………………….. a long break.",
            "description": "After recommend you can write an ing form or a that-clause. You cannot write a to-infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "me to take",
                "taking",
                "that I take"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "52b0cb0f50244e0386ff7a6a379bfce8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy insisted ………………………….. nothing wrong.",
            "description": "We use a that-clause after insist.",
            "answers": [
                "to do",
                "doing",
                "that he did"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fe2bc3e05019411fab1ff15c13118cff"
        },
        {
            "question": "Now that I am getting older, I tend ………………………. things.",
            "description": "We use a to-infinitive after tend.",
            "answers": [
                "forgetting",
                "to forget",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9eed04b45164957a955016f42d9573b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s cut it ………………………..",
            "description": "Here short is the complement of the object it. Object complements are usually adjectives or nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "short",
                "shortly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c0458a14df341da986a4ff831e31887"
        },
        {
            "question": "I find her attitude …………………………",
            "description": "Here strange is the complement of the object attitude. Object complements are usually adjectives or nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "strange",
                "strangely"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b8d23ad3dfee4c789a51b504df12a8f2"
        }
    ]
}